

# Kevin Steven Falencik

#### Contact

#### **Address**

67/2 Lorne Street, Edinburgh

#### **Phone**

07961276427

#### **Email**

kfalencik@gmail.com

#### Additional Skills

- Windows, Mac OS, Linux Ubuntu
- Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, GIMP
- NPM, Gulp, Grunt
- PhpMyAdmin
- Using WCAG (Accessibility standards) while developing

## **Professional Summary**

I'm a 28 years old, Polish front-end developer, living in Edinburgh, Scotland. I'm very passionate about web technologies, with more than 10 years of experience in the field. I started as a more full-stack developer but recently decided to shift my focus to front-end technologies as it better suits my creative side. For more details about me please visit my digital resume page at - kevinfalencik.netlify.com

## Work Experience

Nov 2011 - Jan 2013

#### Droptica (former Advanteo), Gdansk, Poland

Drupal web developer (full-stack),

- Developing and maintaining websites on Drupal 6 & 7
- Writing clean CSS/SASS
- Remote work
- Organising database structures in MySQL
- Developing custom PHP modules and views
- LAMP Unix server
- GIT

Nov 2013 - Mar 2018

#### Starbit, Edinburgh, Scotland

Lead developer (full-stack),

- Developing and maintaining websites on Drupal 7 & Wordpress
- Writing clean CSS/SASS
- Organising database structures in MySQL
- Developing custom PHP modules and views
- Custom jQuery/AJAX plugins
- LAMP Unix server
- GIT
- Maintaining constant communication with the clients
- · Leading a small team of developers

Mar 2018 - Mar 2020

## Kin+Carta (former AmazeRealise), Edinburgh, Scotland

Front-end developer,

- Developing and maintaining a number of projects using front-end frameworks
- · Vue.js, Nuxt.js, React, Angular
- Experience in deploying sites using Netlify
- Writing clean CSS/SASS
- Writing DRY pure JavaScript (ES6) code
- Experience implementing Firestore database and Contentful API
- · Maintaining constant communication with the clients
- Experience using Jira, Fogbugz, Github, Gitlab and similar
- Travelling to different locations for meetings and on-site client work
- Developed a number of side projects during spare time

## Education

Primary School (4 years)

Primary School number 1, Tczew, Poland

Lower Secondary School (3 years)

Gimnazjum number 1, Tczew, Poland

Technical School (4 years)

Complex of technology and communication schools, Gdansk, Poland

Computer Scientist specialising in web applications

University (unfinished, 4 months)

University of Gdansk, Poland

Information Technology

## Languages

English — Fluent

Polish — Native

#### **Hobbies**

- Cycling
- Movies and books
- Video and board games
- Doodling and tattoos
- Playing guitar